G. D. Hsiung papers
Medical Historical Library, Harvey Cushing / John Hay Whitney Medical Library
- Miscellaneous, Series X
  - Photograph books/scrapbooks of people and conferences, Subseries 1
    - Becton-Dickinson Award scrapbook (disbound), 1983-1986 (Box 35)
      - Certificate for serving on the Becton-Dickinson Award Committee, 1986 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - "Progress in Virology Starting 1956 at Yale", 1956-1965 (Box 36)
      Contains photographs of G. D. Hsiung in the laboratory, photographs of the Section of Epidemiology, and photographs of the Department of Epidemiology and Public Health at Yale.
    - "Virology Laboratory," 1965-1978 (Box 36)
      Includes formal group photographs of the staff, formal photographs of G. D. Hsiung, and photographs of students presenting posters at professional meetings, and of laboratory parties. Newspaper clippings are also included.
    - "Experimental Methods in Medical Virology" Course, 1977 (Box 36)
      See Box 16 for other materials on the course. Notebook contains photographs of participants in the laboratory, etc.
    - "Experimental and Diagnostic Methods in Medical Virology" Course, 1979 (Box 35)
      See Box 16 for information on the course. Notebook contains photographs of participants in the laboratory, etc.
    - Clinical Virology Symposium, 1985-1996 (Box 36)
    - Medical and Experimental Virology Course, Virus Research Institute, Hubei Medical College, 1982 (Box 36)
      Photographs of participants, etc. This course was co-taught by Frank Bia who wrote an article for Connecticut Medicine on the experience.
    - "International Workshop on Diagnosis of Viral and Chlamydial Infections," Taiwan, 1994 (Box 36)
    - "Third International Symposium on Viral and Chlamydial Infections," Taiwan, 1999. (Box 36)
    - "International Congress and Symposium, 1957-1976" (Box 37)
    - "Meetings and Conferences, 1979-1982" (Box 37)
    - "Meetings and Conferences, 1983-" (Box 37)
      This scrapbook contains many photographs of students with their posters for poster sessions.
    - Meetings, 1983-1985 (Box 37)
    - Meetings, 1986-1987 (Box 37)
    - Meetings, 1988-1990 (Box 37)
  - Other, Subseries 2
    This box contains leftover materials that did not get incorporated into earlier boxes.
    - G. D. Hsiung, "Proposed Plan for a Virus Research Laboratory", 1965 February 15 (Box 38, Folder 1)
      This carbon copy seems to relate to her work at Yale University. She describes the work she does in her current position at Yale. See Box 8.
    - Course: "Electron Microscopy in the Biological Sciences," Northeastern University, 1967 (Box 38, Folder 2)
      This was a course that Dr. Hsiung took. Folder contains course information and several electron micrographs.
    - G. D. Hsiung: Certificates for Training and for Service Awards, 1968-1991 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Business expenses (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - VA Laboratory Holiday Parties and Other Holiday Parties, 1985-1990 (Box 38, Folder 5)
      Small posters inviting the recipient to a holiday party, and some lists of who was invited.
    - Miscellaneous group photographs, 1963-1997 (Box 38, Folder 6)
      These are professionally taken group photographs, some from the "Diagnostic Virology" course at Yale (1963-1965), and some at the international symposia Hsiung attended in Taiwan.
    - Calendar/Planner, 1989/1990 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Christmas cards, 1989 (Box 38, Folder 8)
      Christmas and other holiday cards that Hsiung received, many from foreign countries, and usually with their envelopes.
    - Christmas cards, 1990 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - Christmas cards, 1991 (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - Christmas cards, 1992 (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - Christmas cards, 1993 (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - Miscellaneous handwritten notes by Hsiung (Box 38, Folder 13)
- Research materials, Series XI
  - Laboratory Research Procedures, Subseries 1
    - Virus Inventory: Freezer Index, 1955-1964 (Box 39, Folder 1)
      Stored records and inventory for ECHO, polio, simian viruses and human viruses. These files illustrate an early period of virology, as some of the viruses listed were state-of-the-art in the 1950s to 1960s. Technical descriptions of file contents here and in later research folders are by Dr. John Booss.
    - Virus Inventory: Dilutions Records, 1955-1964 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Virus Inventory: Standard Dilutions Records, 1955-1964 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Virus Inventory: Poliovirus Stock, 1955-1964 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Virus Inventory: Coxsackie Virus Stock, 1966-1964 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - ECHO Virus Stock (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Virus Inventory: Adenovirus and Myxovirus Stock, 1955-1964 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Reagents and Stocks: General Methods, 1955-1978 (Box 39, Folder 8)
      References, reprints, and procedures for working with monolayer cell cultures, including cultures of poliovirus.
    - Reagents and Stocks: Cell Cultivation, 1955-1978 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Reagents and Stocks: Medium for Trichomonas, 1955-1978 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Reagents and Stocks: 50% Calculation, 1955-1978 (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Plaque Formation for Bottle Cultures, 1960 (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Electron Microscope Procedures, 1963-1968 (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - Pleuropneumonia-like Organisms (PPLO), 1964-1966 (Box 39, Folder 14)
      From a folder labeled "PPLO Psittacosis", procedures and micrographs of pleuropneumonia-like organisms
    - Media, Reagents, Water System Information, 1969-1980 (Box 39, Folder 15)
      Some of content is similar to Laboratory Manual, with additional notes; most of the material is unique. Fundamental information about techniques for studying tissue culture, potentially part of work on 2nd Edition Diagnostic Virology.
    - Leukocytes for Tissue Culture, 1971-1973 (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - Separation of Cells, 1977 (Box 39, Folder 17)
    - Laboratory Manual, 1979-1985 (Box 39, Folder 18)
    - GPE Trypsinization, 1983 (Box 39, Folder 19)
    - Guinea Pig Herpes-Like Virus Purification, 1984-1985 (Box 39, Folder 20)
    - Pathogenesis of GPHLV: Introduction/References, 1986-1987 (Box 39, Folder 21)
      From a folder labeled "Molecular Virology of GPHLV, Hybridization, Pathogenesis of GPHLV", these files contain procedures for slides and hybridization, particularly in connection to guinea pig viruses including guinea pig retrovirus, guinea pig cytomegalovirus, and guinea pig herpes-like virus.
    - Pathogenesis of GPHLV: In Situ Hybridization (Box 39, Folder 22)
    - Pathogenesis of GPHLV: Virus Purification, 1986-1987 (Box 39, Folder 23)
    - Pathogenesis of GPHLV: Electron Microscopy, 1986-1987 (Box 39, Folder 24)
    - Fixing Cells in Suspension, 1987 (Box 39, Folder 25)
    - Immune Electron Microscope (IEM), 1987 (Box 39, Folder 26)
    - In Situ Hybridization: Immunogold-Silver Staining (IGSS) and Avidin-Biotin Complex Immunoperoxidos (ABC-IP), 1987 (Box 39, Folder 27)
      According to John Booss, the procedures in these folders on In Situ Hybridization were state-of-the-art for the time.
    - In-Situ Hybridization: Notes and Drafts, 1987 (Box 39, Folder 28)
    - Laboratory Safety Guidelines, 1989-1990 (Box 39, Folder 29)
  - Experiments, 1956-1997; Subseries 2
    These are annotated photographs of bottles or cells glued on pages, previously organized in three-ringed notebooks. Arranged by rough chronological date. Similar material may be found in "Additional Research Materials," Boxes 50-56.
    - Factors Influencing Plaque Formation: Introduction, 1956-1959; Box 40 (Folder 1)
      From a binder labeled "Effect of pH and Temperature: Polioviruses D and T," this important early work on poliovirus, likely done with Joseph Melnick, contains bottle cultures for studying experimental conditions for polioviruses, among others.
    - Factors Influencing Plaque Formation: Host-cell susceptibility, 1956-1959 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Factors Influencing Plaque Formation: Nutrient Requirements (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Factors Influencing Plaque Formation: Effect of Light, 1956-1959 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Factors Influencing Plaque Formation: Effect of pH and Temperature, 1956-1959 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Factors Influencing Plaque Formation: Poliovirus (Virulent Strains), 1956-1959 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Factors Influencing Plaque Formation: Poliovirus (Avirulent Strains), 1956-1959 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Factors Influencing Plaque Formation: Stool Samples and Isolations, 1956-1959 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Factors Influencing Plaque Formation: Monkey Cords and Isolations, 1956-1959 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Factors Influencing Plaque Formation: Effect of CO2+NaOH, 1956-1959 (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - Factors Influencing Plaque Formation: Recombination, 1956-1959 (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - Kidney Cell Cultures: Animal Kidney Cells, 1957-1959 (Box 40, Folder 12)
      From binder labeled "Human Cell Culture, Kidney Cell Culture, Cultivation of Cells, a record of early tissue culture from different species, including primate, rodent, swine, bovine, canine, avian, and ovine, with photomicrographs of cells from these various animal species as illustration. Additionally, there are detailed illustrations of tissue culture techniques.
    - Kidney Cell Cultures: Human Kidney Cells, 1957-1959 (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - Kidney Cell Cultures: Cultivation of Cells, 1957-1959 (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - X-Ray Irradiation of Cell Cultures: Capuchin Monkey Cultures, 1958 (Box 40, Folder 15)
      From a folder labeled "X-Ray Irradiation Variation and Mutation," this experiment from early in Hsiung's career contains pictures of cells before and after radiation treatment from a variety of animal models, including capuchin, rhesus and patas monkeys as well as mice. Later files feature the stoppered bottle cultures that Hsiung and Melnick developed to incubate viruses, with notes on recognized cytopathic effect.
    - X-Ray Irradiation of Cell Cultures: Rhesus Monkey Cultures (Box 40, Folder 16)
    - X-Ray Irradiation of Cell Cultures: Patas Monkey Cultures, 1958 (Box 40, Folder 17)
    - X-Ray Irradiation of Cell Cultures: Coxsackie B2, 1958 (Box 40, Folder 18)
    - X-Ray Irradiation of Cell Cultures: Plaque Morphology of Rhesus and Patas Cultures, 1958 (Box 40, Folder 19)
    - X-Ray Irradiation of Cell Cultures: Variation and Mutation, 1958 (Box 40, Folder 20)
    - X-Ray Irradiation of Cell Cultures: Mice Cultures, 1958 (Box 40, Folder 21)
    - Isolation and Identification of Viruses: Virus Identification, 1964-1967, 1984 (Box 41, Folder 1)
      From a folder labeled "Isolation and Identification 1964-1967," Adenovirus in HEp-2 cells study and poliovirus/antibodies studies, including procedures, primary data, and case studies from Hsiung's time at NYU in 1966.
    - Isolation and Identification of Viruses: Neutralization, Agaroverlay, "Sudden Death" Cases, 1964-1967 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Isolation and Identification of Viruses: Patient Autopsies, 1964-1967 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Isolation and Identification of Viruses: Antibody Studies, 1964-1967 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Isolation and Identification of Viruses: Adenoviruses, 1964-1967 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Measles and Respiratory Syncytial Virus: Measles, 1965 (Box 41, Folder 6)
      From folder labeled "Measles RS", these files contain tissue cultures, bottle cultures and photomicrographs of measles and respiratory syncytial virus in various animal models and cell types.
    - Measles and Respiratory Syncytial Virus: Respiratory Syncytial Virus (RSV), 1965 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Measles and Respiratory Syncytial Virus: Monkey Measles CPE, 1965 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - DA Myxovirus: Isolation and Identification, 1965 (Box 41, Folder 9)
      From a folder labeled "DA Myxovirus", these files contain images of cell cultures and bottle cultures of various viruses, primarily DA virus. Hsiung was responsible for isolating and contributing DA virus to the American Type Culture Collection (ATCC)
    - DA Myxovirus: Autoinference, 1965 (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - DA Myxovirus: Naples Virus, 1965 (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - DA Myxovirus: Effect of Ether Treatments, 1965 (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - DA Myxovirus: Neutralization of Naples Virus, 1965 (Box 41, Folder 13)
    - DA Myxovirus: Hemadsorption Virus (HA virus), 1965 (Box 41, Folder 14)
    - DA Myxovirus: Newcastle Disease Virus (NDV), 1965 (Box 41, Folder 15)
    - Chronic Bronchitis: Patient Data, 1965 (Box 41, Folder 16)
      This file contains primary data, a partial reduction of data and a brief summary manuscript. The study is associated with Dr. Robert Green.
      Access to this file is restricted due to patient information.
    - Chronic Bronchitis: Reduced Data/Summary (Box 41, Folder 17)
    - Simian Adenovirus Tumors in Hamsters: Tumor Dissection, 1967 (Box 42, Folder 1)
      Experiments on tumors induced by simian adenovirus (SV20) in hamsters, with manuscripts, photographs of tissue and cell cultures, notes and some primary data.
    - Simian Adenovirus Tumors in Hamsters: Cultures from Tumors, 1967 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Simian Adenovirus Tumors in Hamsters: Notes and Data, 1967 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Simian Adenovirus Tumors in Hamsters: SV20 Tumor Cells, 1967 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Simian Adenovirus Tumors in Hamsters: Manuscripts, 1967 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Parainfluenza-3 and Cell Fusion in Hep-2 cells, 1968 (Box 42, Folder 6)
      Study of parainfluenza-3 and cell fusion in Hep-2 cells, with references and photomicrographs
    - Equine Viruses: Primary Data, 1968 (Box 42, Folder 7)
      From a binder labelled "Horse Cultures", this unusual study of naturally occurring equine viruses includes primary data, prints of equine viruses, and a summary of the differences between naturally occurring viruses in hamsters, rabbits and horses.
    - Equine Viruses: Summary, 1968 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Equine Viruses: Prints I, 1968 (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Equine Viruses: Prints II, 1968 (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - Equine Viruses: Prints III, 1968 (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - Chronic Bronchitis: 1967-1968 Data/Minutes, 1967-1970 (Box 42, Folder 12)
      This file contains primary data, procedures, and minutes from the bronchitis study group. This study was associated with Dr. Robert Green.
    - Chronic Bronchitis:1969 Data, 1967-1970 (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - Chronic Bronchitis: 1970 Data, 1967-1970 (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - Chronic Bronchitis: Pleuropneumonia-like Organisms/References, 1967-1970 (Box 42, Folder 15)
    - Reovirus, Arbovirus and Pleuropneumonia-like Organisms: Identification, 1969-1970 (Box 43, Folder 1)
      From folder labeled "Reovirus, Arbovirus" with added "PPLO", this contains pictures and bottle cultures identifying the listed viruses in cultures from animal models. The first tab, reovirus, is labeled "ECHO-10", and contains a variety of ECHO viruses as well as Simian Viruses.
    - Reovirus, Arbovirus and Pleuropneumonia-like Organisms: Reovirus (ECHO-10), 1969-1970 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Reovirus, Arbovirus and Pleuropneumonia-like Organisms: Pleuropneumonia-like Organisms (PPLO), 1969-1970 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Reovirus, Arbovirus and Pleuropneumonia-like Organisms: Arbovirus, 1969-1970 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Simian Cytomegalovirus: Primary Data, 1969 (Box 43, Folder 5)
      This and the next two files contain primary data and photographs on simian cytomegalovirus, comparing it to cytomegalovirus found in rabbits and in humans. The electron micrographs are faded, but the viruses are still recognizable.
    - Simian Cytomegalovirus: Photographs for Comparative Study of Cytomegalovirus (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Simian Cytomegalovirus: Electron Micrographs, 1969 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Leukocyte Cultures: Procedures and Experiments, 1969 (Box 43, Folder 8)
      These files contain procedures and primary data on early work with leukocyte cultures.
    - Leukocyte Cultures: Procedures and Experiments, 1970 (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Leukocyte Cultures: Procedures, 1970-1977 (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Leukocyte Cultures: Soft Agar Method and Experiments, 1971 (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - Antigenic Crossing Between Herpesvirus, 1970-1971 (Box 43, Folder 12)
      Contains some reference materials, including reprints and correspondence, as well as primary data from experiments
    - Macrophages, 1971 (Box 43, Folder 13)
      Cell types and tissue cultures of two different viruses, guinea pig cytomegalovirus and guinea pig herpes simplex
    - Guinea Pig Herpes-Like Virus Gross Protein Analysis, 1972 (Box 43, Folder 14)
      This file contains electron micrographs and a manuscript draft titled "The Purification of a Guinea Pig Herpes-Like Virus and Characterization of its Structural Proteins". The actual date of this file is unknown.
    - Guinea Pig C-Type Virus: Replication of Guinea Pig Herpesvirus in Cell-line Carrying Guinea Pig C-Type Virus, 1972-1974 (Box 43, Folder 15)
      This study looks for a connection between Guinea Pig Leukemia, C-Type Virus and Herpesvirus; the files contain manuscripts, electron micrographs, primary data and data reduction
    - Guinea Pig C-Type Virus: Viral Etiology of Guinea Pig Leukemia, 1972-1974 (Box 43, Folder 16)
    - Guinea Pig C-Type Virus: Reduction of Data, 1972-1974 (Box 43, Folder 17)
    - Guinea Pig C-Type Virus: Primary Data, 1972-1974 (Box 43, Folder 18)
    - Guinea Pig Herpes-Like Virus/Retrovirus, 1972-1977 (Box 43, Folder 19)
      Many different experiments on guinea pig herpes-like virus (HLV) and retrovirus (RV), with procedures, summaries, and primary data
    - Leukocyte Cultures and Guinea Pig Herpesvirus, 1975-1977 (Box 43, Folder 20)
      This file contains primary data from experiments done in collaboration with Aldo Gonzalez-Serva on guinea pig leukocyte cultures
    - Guinea Pig Viruses in Control Animals, 1977 (Box 44, Folder 1)
      Primary data on the presence of viruses in control animals, particularly naturally occurring cytomegalovirus/herpes-like virus in non-sick animals
    - Adenovirus, Herpes, Vaccinia: Prints, 1978 (Box 44, Folder 2)
      From a binder labeled "Adenovirus, Herpes, Vaccinia, Molluscum Contagiosum", quality prints of early enterovirus designations, including Hep 2, adenovirus, APC, EBCO
    - Adenovirus, Herpes, Vaccinia: APC Viruses Prints, 1978 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Adenovirus, Herpes, Vaccinia: ECBO and Canine Hepatitis Prints, 1978 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Comparison of Guinea Pig Cytomegalovirus and Guinea Pig Herpes Like Virus, 1978-1979 (Box 44, Folder 5)
      Contains electron micrographs of cell cultures for comparison of GPCMV and GPHLV, with negatives
    - Comparison of Guinea Pig Cytomegalovirus and Guinea Pig Herpes Like Virus: Charts and Figures, 1978 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Transformation of Guinea Pig Leukocytes: Procedures, 1979 (Box 44, Folder 7)
      Detailed procedures and techniques for transformations of guinea pig leukocytes.
    - Transformation of Guinea Pig Leukocytes: Experiments, 1979 (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - Transformation of Guinea Pig Leukocytes: T.F. Stock Virus, 1979 (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - Transformation of Guinea Pig Leukocytes: Lymphocyte Subcultures (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - Transformation of Guinea Pig Leukocytes: GPE Monolayer Subcultures 01/1980, 1979 (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - Transformation of Guinea Pig Leukocytes: Animal Inoculation, 1979 (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - Infection of Pregnant Guinea Pigs with Cytomegalovirus, 1980 (Box 44, Folder 13)
    - Effect of Acyclovir on HSV-2 and GPHLV: HSV-2 Experiment 1, 1980 (Box 44, Folder 14)
      The files on this antiviral study contain primary data and some data reduction. The guinea pig viruses herpes simplex virus-2 and herpes-like virus were used as models for genital herpes and treated with acyclovir.
    - Effect of Acyclovir on HSV-2 and GPHLV: HSV-2 Experiment 2, 1980 (Box 44, Folder 15)
    - Effect of Acyclovir on HSV-2 and GPHLV: HSV-2 Experiment 3, 1980 (Box 44, Folder 16)
    - Effect of Acyclovir on HSV-2 and GPHLV: HSV-2 Experiment 4, 1980 (Box 44, Folder 17)
    - Effect of Acyclovir on HSV-2 and GPHLV: HSV-2 Experiment 5, 1980 (Box 44, Folder 18)
    - Effect of Acyclovir on HSV-2 and GPHLV: HSV-2 Experiment 6, 1980 (Box 44, Folder 19)
    - Effect of Acyclovir on HSV-2 and GPHLV: HSV-2 Summary, 1980 (Box 44, Folder 20)
    - Effect of Acyclovir on HSV-2 and GPHLV: GPHLV Experiment 1, 1980 (Box 44, Folder 21)
    - Effect of Acyclovir on HSV-2 and GPHLV: GPHLV Experiment 2, 1980 (Box 44, Folder 22)
    - Effect of Acyclovir on HSV-2 and GPHLV: GPHLV Experiment 3 (Box 44, Folder 23)
    - Guinea Pig Herpes-Like Virus T and B Cells, 1983 (Box 45, Folder 1)
      Photomicrographs, slides, and manuscripts as part of a study done in collaboration with Kenneth Dowler on Guinea Pig Herpes-Like Virus and immunosuppression.
    - Cyclophosphamide Immunosuppression of Guinea Pig Herpesvirus, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 2)
      This file contains primary and reduced data, as well as slides, photographs, charts, and graphs, related to the cyclophosphamide immunosuppression study.
    - Retrovirus Growth of Stock: Procedures, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 3)
      From binder labeled "Retrovirus 1984: Growth of Stock", research includes prints, explanation of protocols and article "Polypeptides of BrdU-Induced Guinea Pig Oncornavirus and Particles"
    - Retrovirus Growth of Stock: Prints, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Cyclosporine-A Immunosuppression on Lymphotropic Herpesvirus, 1985 (Box 45, Folder 5)
      This file contains reduced data and a manuscript for an antiviral study of Cyclosporine-A on Guinea Pig Lymphotropic Herpesvirus
    - Guinea Pig Herpes-Like Virus Antiviral Studies: Summary, 1987 (Box 45, Folder 6)
      Summary of antiviral studies being tested on guinea pig herpes-like virus in Dr. Hsiung's laboratory from 1980 to 1986, including antiviral agents ACV, FMAU, BW 1117, BW 767, and UM 102
    - HPMPC, HPMPA, PMEG, DHPG Drug Study: Introduction, 1988-1989 (Box 45, Folder 7)
      From a binder labelled "HPMPC, HPMPA, PMEG, DHPG", primary data on an antiviral drug study for guinea pig cytomegalovirus
    - HPMPC, HPMPA, PMEG, DHPG Drug Study: BMY 40084 and BMY 40085, 1988-1989 (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - HPMPC, HPMPA, PMEG, DHPG Drug Study: BMY 40251 and DHPG, 1988-1989 (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - HPMPC, HPMPA, PMEG, DHPG Drug Study: BMY 40444 and BMY 41671, 1988-1989 (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - 164 and DHPG Experiments, 1988-1989 (Box 45, Folder 11)
      Contains primary data and related paper on experiments with antiviral agents 164 and DHPG
    - Effect of Compound 102 and 164 on Guinea Pig Cytomegalovirus: Experiment Data, 1989 (Box 45, Folder 12)
      Primarily Electron micrographs, with explanation of objectives, procedure, and some data
    - Effect of Compound 102 and 164 on Guinea Pig Cytomegalovirus: Virus Control Electron Micrographs, 1989 (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - Effect of Compound 102 and 164 on Guinea Pig Cytomegalovirus: Compound 102 Electron Micrographs, 1989 (Box 45, Folder 14)
    - Effect of Compound 102 and 164 on Guinea Pig Cytomegalovirus: Compound 164 Electron Micrographs (Box 45, Folder 15)
    - Effect of Compound 102 and 164 on Guinea Pig Cytomegalovirus: 102 and 164 Electron Micrographs, 1989 (Box 45, Folder 16)
    - Evaluation of Antiviral Activity of Compound HPMPC on GPCMV in vivo, 1989 (Box 45, Folder 17)
      Antiviral drug studies on the effect of agent HPMPC on GPCMV, experiments 5 and 6; includes protocol and methodology, primary data, some data reduction
    - 2'-nor-cGMP/DHPG Combination Study: Protocols, 1990 (Box 46, Folder 1)
      Antiviral drug testing of 2'-nor-cGMP and DHPG, including primary data, correspondence, protocols, and resulting publications, with additional guinea pig doodles
    - 2'-nor-cGMP/DHPG Combination Study: Experiments I and II, 1990 (Box 46, Folder 2)